[
    {
        "id": "01",
        "question": "How is the kanji '持って行きます' read in word?",
        "answer": "Брати з собою"
    },
    {
        "id": "02",
        "question": "How is the kanji '持って来ます' read in word?",
        "answer": "Приносити з собою"
    },
    {
        "id": "03",
        "question": "How is the kanji '心配します' read in word?",
        "answer": "Хвилюватись"
    },
    {
        "id": "04",
        "question": "How is the kanji '心配' read in word?",
        "answer": "хвилювання"
    },
    {
        "id": "05",
        "question": "How is the kanji '答えます' read in word?",
        "answer": "Відповідати"
    },
    {
        "id": "06",
        "question": "How is the kanji '答え' read in word?",
        "answer": "відповідь"
    },
    {
        "id": "07",
        "question": "How is the kanji '吐き気' read in word?",
        "answer": "Нудота"
    },
    {
        "id": "08",
        "question": "How is the kanji '吐き気がします' read in word?",
        "answer": "відчувати нудоту"
    },
    {
        "id": "09",
        "question": "How is the kanji '咳' read in word?",
        "answer": "Кашель"
    },
    {
        "id": "10",
        "question": "How is the kanji '咳がでます' read in word?",
        "answer": "кашляти"
    },
    {
        "id": "11",
        "question": "How is the kanji 'お腹' read in word?",
        "answer": "Живіт"
    },
    {
        "id": "12",
        "question": "How is the kanji '歯' read in word?",
        "answer": "Зуб"
    },
    {
        "id": "13",
        "question": "How is the kanji '熱' read in word?",
        "answer": "Жар, гарячка"
    },
    {
        "id": "14",
        "question": "How is the kanji '火傷' read in word?",
        "answer": "Опік"
    }
]